engineershub.in 2015-11-14

# Privacy Policy - Terms and Conditions - EngineersHub

##  Privacy Policy 

#### REGISTRATION

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a username and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as your email address).

EngineersHub is the sole owner of the contact and usage information collected on engineershub.com. Engineers Hub collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

#### THIRD PARTY AUTHENTICATION

If you decide to register through or otherwise grant access to a third party social networking or authentication service that we may make available (“Authentication Service”), such as Facebook or Google, we will collect certain personal information that you have provided to the Authentication Service (such as your name, email address and other information you make available via the Authentication Service) from the account you have with the Authentication Service. The personal information collected from the Authentication Service may be used to register you for the Web site and to provide some of the features of the Web site. You may revoke EngineersHub access to your account on the Authentication Service at any time by updating the appropriate settings in the account preferences of the respective Authentication Service. You understand that certain features of the Web site may not be available to you if you choose to remove EngineersHub access to your account with the Authentication Service.

#### LOG FILES

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. However, your account is associated with any and all contributions you make to the site and you are responsible for adhering to all presently published IP policies.

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's 'help' file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your User Name and Passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. If you register through, or otherwise provide EngineersHub with access to, an Authentication Service, we may store the authorization token provided to EngineersHub by the Authentication Service in order to improve your experience with the Web site. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by EngineersHub only.

#### PROFILE

We store information that we collect through registration and the contributions you make to the community to create a 'profile' of your preferences and activities, to serve the community and to enforce IP and use policies. All contributions you make on the site are linked to your user profile and login/screen name. If you have shared your profile, any member of the site can view your profile and the information stored there (except your password) and all of your published contributions (but not your unpublished contributions). Even if you choose to keep your profile private, all members can see your published contributions and that your screen name is associated with the contribution. While we may make available certain privacy settings for your profile, we cannot guarantee that any information that you provide to us in your profile will not be accessible by third parties, such as by unauthorized third party access or other access.

#### USES OF INFORMATION

EngineersHub collects personal information that you disclose when you register with the site, when you grant access to an Authentication Service, and through your use of the services on the site. EngineersHub automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, EngineersHub cookies, the contributions you make and the page you request. EngineersHub uses information for the following general purposes, to: monitor traffic, improve our services, enforce terms of use and IP policies, contact you, and conduct research.

### COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE SITE

#### SERVICE-RELATED ANNOUNCEMENTS

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request as reasonable.

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

#### PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

EngineersHub is not in the business of selling your personal information. We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties as long as you keep your user profile private and we do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you collected in connection with your use of the EngineersHub Website with other people or entities, except as otherwise specified.

We may share your personally identifiable information with companies that provide services to us in connection with developing, operating and maintaining the Web site and our business, including outside vendors, contractors, and agents who help us manage our business activities. We only authorize such entities to use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for no other purpose than to provide us necessary services.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct or update your profile by making the change on our member information page ('My EngineersHub') and you may delete or deactivate your profile by sending an e-mail to support@engineershub.in or by contacting us through any method described in the EngineersHub Contact Page.

#### SECURITY

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@engineershub.in.

#### BUSINESS TRANSITIONS

In the event EngineersHub goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another entity, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

### CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

We reserve the right to amend or modify our privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@engineershub.in](mailto:support@engineershub.in)
